jobjet.in 2015-06-19

# Privacy Policy

jobjet.in is website designed as a resource to help students and all to know about latest Employment News, Govt Jobs, Private Jobs, Exams, Career, Online Test and Tutorials etc. The site mainly concentrated on Employment News, Govt Jobs, Private Jobs, Exams, Career and more. jobjet.in aims to be a great platform for Job hunters without getting involved in legal suits. So, here is the privacy policy for www.jobjet.in

The content provided by www.jobjet.in is exclusively for informational purposes only and we hold no right whatever for all the activity that a visitor (you) does on other web pages linked from www.jobjet.in

Since we verify every information at the time of publishing them on jobjet.in and we (jobjet.in) can’t be held any response for any type of changes made to original rules a later dates of any post or article. It’s your task to make sure and take care of official announcement by visiting official website.

 **Privacy Policy:**

 ****If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at ravi.garnepally@gmail.com At www.jobjet.in , the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.jobjet.in and how it is used.

 **Log Files:**

 ****Like many other Web sites, jobjet.in makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

 **Double Click DART Cookie:**

Google as a third party vendor uses cookies to serve ads on www.jobjet.in  
Google use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to jobjet.in. and other sites on the Internet.

Users may choose out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.  
Google Adsense These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on jobjet.in send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party vendors ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. jobjet.in has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

Users should consult the particular privacy policies of these intermediary ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for commands about how to avoid of assured practices. jobjet.in privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. If, you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your personal browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ relevant websites.
